"Ura Sunday"
This is so boring, Mob.
"Ura Sunday" Doesn't that just mean
no one's being bothered by spirits?
I hate this.
It's really peaceful.
But we need food on our table!
We have to make a move.
"You don't know what true fear is" "Urban
Legends" "Enter" We have to make a move.
"You don't know what true
fear is" "Urban Legends" "Enter"
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
"Urban Legends
- Encountering Rumors~"
Urban legends?
Yeah. Surely you've discussed some
with friends at some point.
I haven't, actually.
Really? They were super popular
when I was a kid.
Like Hanako-san in the bathroom
or the human-faced dog...
Or, if you want something newer, the Dragger.
We'll look up sighting reports online
and follow these urban legends.
So it's like when we went
to find the tsuchinoko?
Not quite.
The Dragger is completely made up.
She doesn't exist.
Then, why...
Places where urban legends are popular
tend to have a lot of people
who easily believe in the supernatural.
Meaning they're gold mines
for exorcism jobs.
You're so excited about
this Schadenfreude search.
The key to successful
walk-in sales is a smile!
"Spiritual Advice"
That table is really low.
I didn't think this through.
Those are some cold stares...
Uh, we might be bothering the pedestrians.
Hey, you two.
Who said you could
conduct your business here?
You dare set up shop here knowing that I,
"Rising Sun Spiritual Union" "Shinra Banshomaru"
"Rising Sun Spiritual Union"
"Shinra Banshomaru"
"Rising Sun Spiritual Union" "Shinra Banshomaru" Shinra Banshomaru,
the greatest psychic of this century, hold jurisdiction here?
"Rising Sun Spiritual Union"
"Shinra Banshomaru"
"Rising Sun Spiritual Union" "Shinra Banshomaru"
He's the "greatest of this century,” too?
What do you mean, jurisdiction?
You're not a member of
the Rising Sun Spiritual Union?
I'm a freelancer. The name's Reigen Arataka.
If you're also running
a spirit con--business,
could you introduce me to some clients?
I haven't had too many lately.
I'm not about to help a business rival.
Begone at once!
I respectfully decline.
What authority do you have?
"Free psychic readings"”
This is clearly a traffic violation.
You guys have no right to bring up the law.
And what do you mean by that?
Um...
Are you psychics?
Yes?
I'd like to discuss something with you.
--Happy to help you out, ma'am!
--But of course!
So what did you want to discuss?
I've always been susceptible to spirits.
I often attract ghosts and other
strange phenomena near me.
Even as we speak,
there's something next to me...
Next to you? I don't--
There definitely is. I see it.
Hey, stop making things up.
What did you say, you swine?
Give me a break. Fakes like you
make my job so much harder.
Right, Mob?
It's the spirit of a middle-aged man.
Let's get back on track.
Thank goodness. You're actual psychics.
When I asked about it on the Internet,
all I got was irresponsible advice.
What are you writing?
I can't believe I never thought about a website.
I'll make one as soon as I'm home.
And lately, I've been feeling a really bad aura.
I've only been able to get by thanks to
having a plate of salt in my apartment.
I see. Textbooks confirm
the effectiveness of piles of salt.
Indeed. Even as we speak,
the sodium from this pile of French fries
is mitigating the negative effects.
Mob, don't eat too many of those.
But then I realized that the reason
this eerie feeling has gotten worse lately
is because of the sudden spread of
urban legends around this city.
"Cuticle City Urban Legends” "Human-Faced Dog"
"Dash Granny" "The Red Raincoat" "The Dragger"
"Cuticle City Urban Legends" "Human-Faced Dog" "Dash Granny" "The Red
Raincoat" "The Dragger" Human-Faced Dog, Dash Granny, the Red Raincoat,
"Cuticle City Urban Legends” "Human-Faced Dog"
"Dash Granny" "The Red Raincoat" "The Dragger"
"Cuticle City Urban Legends" "Human-Faced Dog" "Dash Granny"
"The Red Raincoat" "The Dragger" and of course... the Dragger.
"Cuticle City Urban Legends” "Human-Faced Dog"
"Dash Granny" "The Red Raincoat" "The Dragger"
Please, eliminate all
of these urban legends.
Come on... Who would take
such an impossible request?
Please leave it to me, Reigen Arataka!
I'll make sure they're wiped off
the face of the Earth!
So, which course would you like to go with?
--"Course"?
--I recommend this weekend combo deal...
I must say, I was surprised
you accepted a request like that.
And 20,000 yen if the request works out?
You'd ask for about that much, wouldn't you?
I generally start at 200,000.
If I actually took on this request,
it'd be more than 500,000--
Well, you'll still be helping me with this.
I'm sorry? What did he just say?
Let's get going. If we keep wasting time,
the sun's gonna go down.
Um... Shinrin Maruo, was it?
It's Shinra Banshomaru,
and I'm not going to help you!
"Shinra Banshomaru" It's Shinra
Banshomaru, and I'm not going to help you!
"Shinra Banshomaru"
"Shinra Banshomaru" You heard her
out with me, so don't you dare run away.
"Shinra Banshomaru"
That makes no sense.
I'll make sure you get your cut.
Let's split up and do some investigating.
"New Star of the Psychic World"
"New Star of the Psychic World" Let's remember
the three Cs: contact, communicate, and consult.
Let's remember the three Cs:
contact, communicate, and consult.
Oh, fine.
I'll consider this charity work
and help you out.
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Like you have anything better to do.
Mob, is Dimple around?
Dimple, you're being summoned.
What do you want?
I'm making myself less visible
because I'm sick of talking to you.
Come on, don't be like that.
We're work buddies.
How?!
You just order me around--
Tail that chubster using
that stealth mode of yours.
Why should 1?
If he runs off, just let him go.
Nah, I bet he's a super serious moron
that does everything by the book.
Meaning, if something were to happen to him,
it'd be my fault for making him do this.
Please, Dimple.
It'd be better to avoid any accidents.
"Watch out for suspicious people" Please,
Dimple. It'd be better to avoid any accidents.
"Watch out for suspicious people"
Oh, fine.
This is give and take.
"Watch out for suspicious people"
"Watch out for suspicious people" You're going to have
to listen to one of my demands sometime soon, Shigeo!
You're going to have to listen to one
of my demands sometime soon, Shigeo!
What's the matter, Mob?
Well, it's like the client said.
Something's weird about this town.
There might actually be something here.
Why did we come to an Internet café?
If I go around questioning kids,
people might think I'm someone suspicious.
"Cuticle Middle School Dark Message Board” "2950. Another crappy day~" "My teacher is so frickin' annoying. Who do they
think they are, bossing me around every day?"” If I go around questioning kids, people might think I'm someone suspicious.
"Cuticle Middle School Dark Message Board” "2950. Another crappy day~" "My teacher
is so frickin' annoying. Who do they think they are, bossing me around every day?"”
"Cuticle Middle School Dark Message Board” "2950. Another crappy day~" "My teacher is so frickin' annoying.
Who do they think they are, bossing me around every day?"” Wow. It's all just a bunch of complaints.
Wow. It's all just a bunch of complaints.
"2953. Hey, did you see?” "The old guy with the bad eyes who lives on Fourth
has a human-faced dog lololol Wow. It's all just a bunch of complaints.
"2953. Hey, did you see?" "The old guy with the bad
eyes who lives on Fourth has a human-faced dog lololol"
"2953. Hey, did you see?” "The old guy with the bad eyes who lives on Fourth has a
human-faced dog lololol There must be something useful within this barrage of complaints...
There must be something useful
within this barrage of complaints...
"2956. This is scary "Did you hear that the dash granny showed up in OO
Tunnel?” There must be something useful within this barrage of complaints...
"2956. This is scary"” "Did you hear that
the dash granny showed up in OO Tunnel?"
"2956. This is scary "Did you hear that the
dash granny showed up in OO Tunnel?” Hey, look!
Hey, look!
"Cuticle Park"
Sighting report!
We saw an old guy in red earlier.
He tried to talk to us, so we ran away.
What? When?!
Wh-Where? Where was he?!
Hey, that hurts! Let go!
Why's this guy breathing so heavily?
O-Oh, I'm sorry. I just got a bit excited...
Uh, wait, I didn't mean excited
in that kind of way...
Why are you looking at me like that?
We're leaving now.
Hey! You mustn't go alone! You're girls!
Get away from us!
This guy's a pervert!
Hey, stop that!
I'm not--
Huh? What?
"Stare"
"Stare Stare"
Huh? What?
N-No! I'm not a pervert!
I'm an extremely well-known psychic!
Did he just say psychic?
Like that doesn't sound shady...
Ow! Hey, don't throw rocks at me!
--Ow!
--That guy was so gross.
Wait! I need that lead!
Crap! The girls I was after!
Wait, was that...
Hold it right there!
You must be the Red Raincoat!
Don't get in my way!
There's nothing fun about
exposing myself to another guy!
So you're a flasher who goes after children?
You filthy criminal!
This is awesome! Creep versus creep!
Get a video of this!
I may not look it, but I was vice captain
of the sumo club in grade school!
I give up! I give up, so let me go!
You got me...
Or so you thought...
I was on the track team
in middle school, fatty!
Talk about playing dirty.
But damn, he's fast.
"Terror"
This is the human-faced dog?
That looks like marker.
I guess the sighting report was fake.
No, this is definitely the human-faced dog.
What do you mean?
This is usually how rumors go.
To grade and middle school kids,
this is the real deal.
Hey, someone's at our
human-faced dog's house.
We should charge admission.
Whose dog is this?
The old guy who lives here.
His eyes are bad, so he hasn't noticed
we scribbled on its face.
A-Are you his grandkids?
Huh? What gave you that idea?
Hey, you little shits!
I'll kick your asses the next time
you try to draw on this dog's face!
So he says after he actually hit us.
We're gonna tell the PTA on you.
Yeah, just try it.
You know what this world needs?
Adults who can keep you little shits in line!
Don't think that I, Suzuki Taro, am going
to be a pushover like your teachers.
But you use a fake name anyway?
You'll give Terror a bath?
What a nice young man.
Was he that dirty? Then, I guess
I'll take you up on your offer.
Here, Terror.
Look at him happily wag his tail
with his ominous-sounding name.
Now, then... We'll need before and after
pictures for our progress report.
I wonder if he just likes dogs.
Did you know it was just
a prank to begin with?
Of course I did.
Were you actually looking for
a dog with a person's face?
There, there.
"Boney Bones" "Dog Shampoo”
"Nom" "Dirt-be-gone” There, there.
"Nom" "Dirt-be-gone”
"Boney Bones" "Dog Shampoo" "Nom" "Dirt-be-gone"
Let's see if we can get some hot water for him.
"Boney Bones" "Dog Shampoo”
"Nom" "Dirt-be-gone”
What? You outta breath?
Too bad for you. I may have been
in the sumo club in grade school,
but in middle school,
I was on the table tennis team!
I'm plenty confident about my stamina!
You're so out of breath, though.
Why are you chasing me?
This has nothing to do with you.
Ever heard of citizen's arrest?
Even a civilian can arrest
a criminal in the act.
Let the blades of justice
strike you down, you pervert!
You seriously thought you caught me?
I led you here on purpose!
I will admit, this all started
as an unusual fetish.
But before long, I started finding pleasure
in rumors of me spreading around town.
I felt like some kind of celebrity!
Just by wearing this raincoat,
I feel unstoppable!
You wanna turn me in to the police?
I'd love to see you try!
He passed out.
But he and others saw my face, which will
make things harder for me in this town.
Guess it's time to leave.
"No Trespassing"
Who the hell are you?
Did you see everything?
Hey, aren't you thirsty?
What, it's just some crazy bitch?
Yeah...
Never been thirstier!
I'll let you drink until you explode, then!
"Spirit Hold"
Spirit Hold! There, now you can't move!
Damn it! I've not recovered from being tased!
Wha--
Where'd she go?!
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
Guess Reigen was right
to send me as insurance!
Talk about pressure...
Her aura's stabbing me left and right.
Guess I'll try to drag out all
of this guy's latent powers.
Hey, aren't you thirsty?!
You tr yin' to hit on me?
I'm not a fan of forceful girls!
Take that!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
To think his manual would
save him this way...
"Spiritual Worldism for Psychics" To
think his manual would save him this way...
"Spiritual Worldism
for Psychics"
His life comes first...
He'll happily turn tail and run away!
I need to send an SOS!
There, all clean.
Mob, how did you get that wet?
I shouldn't have helped.
Hello, this is Reigen.
Hey, did you get any info...
Let's go.
The Dragger showed up.
No wonder she's trending
in the urban legends world.
Maybe because she's all over social media,
she's got way more energy fueling her.
And now she's going for function over form.
His Achilles tendon just snapped!
You damn fatty... You need to exercise more.
Please, Dimple.
If I let this guy die,
Shigeo will lose faith in me.
And I can't let that happen!
He's going to be even bigger someday.
I can't mess up at a place like this.
Oh, shit.
Thanks, Dimple.
Wow, so that's the Dragger?
Is that actually her?
I need to get a photo for proof.
Huh?
She's not showing up on my screen.
She ran!
That's a monster born from rumors.
You can't classify her as real or fake.
What do you mean?
The imagination of the masses,
and their fear and curiosity,
is what gave birth to her.
Her looks and her strength
were all decided by humans!
So you're saying their imagination
became reality?
Th-That's right...
And since we know about the Dragger,
we won't be able to exorcise her.
Huh? Why?
Wasn't there a time as a kid when you
were frightened by rumors about her?
True...
The Dragger would appear before kids
heading home from school,
snatching them up and
dragging them into the bog...
I didn't believe in Santa Claus,
but thinking about her on rainy days
as I passed street corners
would give me goosebumps, too.
That fear is still burned into our brains.
We're even trembling as we speak.
So I'm breaking out in a cold sweat
because I'm scared deep down?
Powers used in fear only empower its source.
My spiritual powers did nothing.
She grows by absorbing the powers
of those who fear her.
Attacking her is futile.
Then we have no choice but to run.
Mob, temporary retreat...
Wh-What is this?!
I'm stuck!
This must be her doing.
--She's huge!
--What?!
Didn't you hear him, Mob?
Your powers will be absorbed, too!
Wait, hang on a sec...
It's actually working!
I see... Shigeo...
He's detached from urban legends, fads,
and other hot topics among people.
He's completely out of the loop!
So he has no idea
what makes the Dragger so scary!
It's a ghost that appears
on rainy days, right?
It's not exactly not scary.
You don't get it!
The Dragger has a grip strength
of 500 kilograms!
Once she grabs you, you can't escape!
And she can swim 100 meters in 20 seconds!
Oh, so that's the kind of character she is.
What, you think she's some
kind of OC or something?
You should at least pretend to be
scared or shocked by these things.
This is why nobody clues you in.
But you used to say that
I didn't have to be like others.
Lip service gains importance as you grow up.
I got injured while I was unconscious?
Anyway, thanks. That was a valuable experience.
I'm going to the police now to
talk to them about the flasher.
Guess this is goodbye.
Ow!
Yeah, take care.
Well, I guess we should check out
Dash Granny before we leave.
Looks like we got here at the perfect time.
Keep your guard up.
There she is! She actually showed up!
Mob! Exorcise her!
Huh? One more time...
--Huh?
--What's wrong, Shigeo?
--She's coming! Hey!
Oh, no... I can't exorcise her...
The Dragger doesn't even compare...
She's too powerful.
What?!
Hey, come on now...
What do we do?
There's only one thing
we can do! Get away! Run!
Hey, what happens if she catches up?
Apparently, she jumps on your back
and strangles you to death!
Run! Run! She's catching up!
Step on it, Mob!
Turns out she was just
some old lady running...
Couldn't you have used your powers
to teleport or something?
Why are you crying?
"Scraped his face"
Because... I run every day...
But that old lady beat me!
"Ding..."
It's not a competition, man.
Well, I got that old lady's picture,
so I guess our work here's done.
Dash Granny would become Mob's first
traumatic experience with urban legends.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Some days later"
"Some days later" It's finally done!
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
"Some days later"
"Some days later" Take a look, Mob.
Take a look, Mob.
Now we'll get even more jobs!
What is this?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The star psychic of the 21st century
who defeated the Dragger" "Welcome to Reigen Arataka's homepage!" What is this?
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The star psychic of the 21st
century who defeated the Dragger" "Welcome to Reigen Arataka's homepage!"!
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office "The star psychic of the 21st century who
defeated the Dragger" "Welcome to Reigen Arataka's homepage! It's shady as hell!
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The star psychic of the 21st
century who defeated the Dragger" "Welcome to Reigen Arataka's homepage!"!
I spilled a seed and lost sight of it
I'll find it using the color it's dyed in
and watch it grow
It immediately returned
to the palm of my hand
But it's still too light and too frail
to reach for the skies
The world coldly drains away all the heat
The bright sunshine just isn't enough
The memories are closing off what lies ahead
Shake off their warmth
and set off into the distance
If I let it wither, it'd be over just like that
But my hope just doesn't fade away
Yes! I'm getting one job after another
because of my web page!
But wait, Mob's been acting a bit weird.
What's wrong, Mob?
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 |l Episode 3:
"One Danger After Another
- Degeneration~."
- Degeneration~"
"One Danger After Another - Degeneration~"
Recording it? That's also a wise decision.
"One Danger After Another
- Degeneration~"